Can you track him, Melone? Yes.
I've got a decent blood sample now.
From Bucciarati.
When is this piece of
junk gonna get moving?
Uh, please forgive us for the delay.
A replacement driver's on
his way this very moment.
Huh?
What happened to the other guy?
I can't take any more of this noise.
Can't the parents do something
about that wailing teat ruiner?
Boarding with these
riffraff was such a mistake.
Ciao. Huh?
So, miss, are you in decent shape or what?
What the hell do you think
you're doing in here?
You're sitting in my private cabin.
Open your eyes and read what's
written on the damn door.
Do you have anything with you that
has your date of birth written on it?
Uh. Oh?
Hey, just what the hell are you doing?
So you were born on march 10th 1977 you're
24 this is molto bellissimo
excellent vintage.
Kick your grubby mitts off
my property and get out!
Very nice the force put into that
rather zesty slap confirms my theory.
You're in perfect condition
just what i need just
sublime and judging from
your delicious digits your
blood type is oh right i
don't need your name and i
don't give a single shit
about your pedigree either
what's absolutely crucial
is your health condition
date of birth and knowing
your blood type a pisces
in type o bucciarati is
an aries in type a which
means the two of you are
utterly incompatible this is
perfection it's divine even
you're clearly a fan of
cigs and booze do you do any
drugs what about narcotics
if you tell me you do then
there's nothing more to
say here than hey lady
could you shut your knob and
listen how you answer the
next question will determine
our success this is a question
of personal preference
which one would you
fancy you've heard of the
ancient Indian Sanskrit
text known as the Kama Star,
yes?
It includes more than 48 erotic positions.
One cannot underestimate their importance.
It is the crucial first step
in creating a stellar child.
Now choose.
Baby head! Help me!
Someone help me!
You are going to be a star.
A bloodthirsty star.
De Mordo.
We will continue to fight.
We will fight with our enemies!
Fighting God!
Criminy?
What's with all the doom and gloom
weighing everyone down all of a sudden?
Did Bucciarati say something he shouldn't
have to Trish to make her angry?
No.
I think she's in this funk because
Bucciarati is actually staying quiet.
Trish is being forced to come
to terms with her innate powers.
And then there's her enigmatic father.
Obviously, she has a lot on her mind.
Bucciarati has his hands tied when it comes
to bringing up anything of that nature,
though.
Somehow, I have to find a way
to learn more about her powers.
Surely they'll shine a light
on the boss's identity.
She's held tough through all of this.
What strength of will.
Mista!
Number two and number three
are being total food hoarders!
You have to tell them to
share their hamburger with us!
What do you mean, bud?
There's not a scrap of food
to speak of in here, huh?
Where the hell did you two get that?
Oh, don't tell me.
Hmm?
Now where the heck could
my burger have run off to?
Hmm?
What's that poking out
from under the seat?
Oh, shit!
A turtle?
Huh?
What's this on its back?
What are we gonna do, Mista?
I have a bad feeling about this.
What's going on?
Mista, you were supposed to watch
the ceiling, so what happened?
Huh? Me?
Can't really say.
I know I should have been on watch,
but I was dealing with something else.
From all that racket outside,
my guess is the truck stopped.
What happened to me?
This is no!
Don't tell me that bastard!
What a relief!
I thought he might have tried.
Something that guy was a damn nutcase!
What was that twisted
degenerate playing at?
He thinks he can scare me and
live to tell the freaking tale!
If I ever see that pervert
again, I'll murder him!
Damn it!
Hello!
Are you the conductor of this train?
I don't care if you're busy!
Drop everything and come to my cabin!
So we've got a baby!
Mother dearest is teaching it well!
Baby heads first!
Little
one. Fantastico.
He's already responding to
Mama's violent inclinations.
Remember, Mother knows best!
Listen, you idiot!
I was assaulted by some creepy pervert!
He just waltzed in!
Which
means your shitty cabins
could use some better locks!
Look at the weld he gave me!
I could scream!
That piece of shit!
I'm taking that guy down!
Piece of shit?
What do those words mean? Damn that prick!
Let's get started.
Now please pay attention.
This is Mr. Lion.
He is the king of the jungle.
Over here is Mr.
Elephant, along with Mr.
Giraffe.
And the striped one is Mr. Zebra.
Next, what have we here?
This is what the word
murder means. Makes sense?
It means to kill or to
put an end to something.
Now, these are some things the kids do.
playing with tops, baseball,
bowling, and ice skating.
Look at all the fun things you
can do with those activities.
These boys here are pieces of shit.
When it's one, they're a piece of shit,
but two or more are called pieces of shit.
If you're getting this,
know that the way in which you kill
them is totally up to your discretion.
Just remember, no harm is to
befall this girl named Trish.
She's to be captured.
Also, there's a new guy with
them that we don't have data on.
He'll be with Bucciarati.
Make sure you seek them
both out and end them.
What the hell do you mean?
Just take your damn piss.
Taking leaks is what babies do.
Unless I'm losing it, the lock
doesn't seem to have been broken.
What the hell is this wet stuff?
Damn this train, now weird
shit's leaking from the roof?
But ma 'am, there's nothing there.
Ugh! Gross! It reeks!
What is this?
It's disgusting! Signora?
It appears that she is.
Well, that being so, what
would you say about her?
Yes!
Di molto! Fantabulous!
You're a good little student!
Hmm?
Be patient.
It's too early for that.
There's still much left for you to learn.
Didn't I say not yet you'll have to wait I
can't take this anymore
I won't spend another
second on this damn train
but you can bet I'll
sue the train company and
hold them accountable!
I could have a concussion for all I know?
That's bizarre why can't I
Her parenting was too good!
It's great that she taught the little psycho
in training the importance of killing,
but she did it too soon!
Huh?
Hey, wait!
Just what am I going to do with you?
But I admit you're a talented bambino.
Thanks to Bucciarati's DNA sample, the
automatic tracking is well underway.
You gotta put in the work,
but Baby Head's offspring is the
pinnacle of long-range stands.
Yes, all will perish before your power.
Let's just steal one
already. Are you stupid?
Sure, why don't we just
announce ourselves to the enemy?
They'll ambush us and that'll be that.
I hate to say this, but
Fugo's got a real good point.
Then let's hear what
Bucciarati wants us to do.
Hey, what are you doing, Giorno?
Driving off with one of
these would be too obvious.
However, if we were to
take a hundred of them...
What do you think happens
when multiple cars vanish?
But the cars have been dismantled?
and the parts are scattered
all over the city and beyond.
Tracking down the stolen cars
gets a lot more complicated,
which gives us plenty of
time to get to Venice.
I guess that makes sense.
Well, it definitely beats us hitchhiking.
I suppose it's settled then.
Giorno, I'll leave it to
you to tell Bucciarati.
Here, take him.
We're gonna go get a car.
Please get down from there.
It's too dangerous for you to leave
Listen, Mr.
Bucciarati, I have a question
for you It's kind of dumb,
but even so, I hope you'll be willing
to answer it What's the question?
Why isn't there a bathroom
in this stuffy place?
And please don't say you're
expecting me to wear a diaper?
Of course I'm not, but
you do make a good point.
Thank goodness, I knew
you were reasonable!
This closet will be our bathroom.
Have at it!
I assumed you needed to use it.
I don't really know where this portal
leads, but I'm sure the turtle will be fine.
It might actually be good for him, huh?
What do you mean?
Please tell me you're
not suggesting that I?
Bucciarati, we'll be traveling by car now.
Right.
Once the area's secured, we can leave.
Understood.
Where did that bike come from?
And where'd the driver go?
Giorno, something wrong?
Trish?
What the hell?
Trish!
Syria!
Hang on!
Zipper!
Shit!
We've got a long-range stand on our hands.
But its power isn't being
kept in check by a user.
What's going...
Bucciarati, be extra careful.
A bike just appeared out of nowhere.
Hmm?
Are you there?
They vanished! Bucciarati!
Where's Trish? Trish!
Impossible!
I've had the turtle the entire time!
There's no way I wouldn't
have seen them exit!
Could something have stolen
them right from under my nose?
Time to get to work, Golden Wind!
Di molto!
Bravissimo, baby head!
Now make yourself scarce
till you can slip away.
There's a mystery man?
Ah, then that must be the new guy.
Well, if he finds you, you'll have
no choice but to take him out.
As you wish, but you must move in
silence lest the others find you.
Holding on to Trish is a must,
but just to be safe, I'll
have them head over as well.
I could have sworn I sensed a...
Oh, you did.
Heads up!
There's something trying to attack...
What?
Something removed my throat!
Could you hurry it up? Bite me.
Fugo, is something wrong?
Giorno's just waving.
I'm sure Bucciarati just wants us to hurry
up with the car so we can hit the road.
Would you all take a chill pill?
The motor, that's fantastic.
What the hell?
The cabinet's gone and still no stand?
What's going on?
And why am I not able to
see it when it attacks me?
How's he hiding it,
dislodging pieces of my body?
No, could he be?
You got his leg and eye too, huh?
Demolto, wonderful!
Now back to Poppa, baby head.
What's this now?
I'm not following what you're getting at.
Living organism?
The rules of the living and the
dead don't apply to stands like you.
Like I thought, it was the cabinet.
I get it now.
I was looking at my attacker the
entire time, but didn't realize it.
He attacks by disassembling the human body
and rearranging the pieces
into something else.
Don't freak out.
Anyway, at this point, what
difference does it make?
That rookie hasn't been breathing for
a while now, and he's missing a leg.
Just get rid of him and grab the
turtle so Trish remains your captive.
Roger.
Golden wind!
It splits itself apart
to dodge, which means...
The guys...
I have to... tell them!
Did I get it?
Nope, that was just your standard rock.
Shit.
At this rate, it's gonna
get away with Trish.
And once it does, it'll
probably kill Bucciarati!
It's got a freakish amount of power!
Can we really beat this thing?
I'll leave this neophyte's body here.
Everything's gone totally
according to plan.
The girl is mine and no one is the wiser.
Di molto! Great!
I'll be seeing you soon, Melone.
Wait for me on the train.
Rearranging the human
body into other objects,
your powers just sparked a terrific idea.
You know, now that I think about it,
your abilities aren't all that
dissimilar from my golden wind.
We both have the power to create something
entirely new you've taught me a lot and
your tenacious spirit pushed me to the
absolute brink to put
it like this i'd say you
pushed me to be better
melone are you still
on the line it completely slipped my mind
but i just now figured
out how the new guy's
power works what's this about the new guy
What are you talking about baby head why
do you care about the dead newbie his
eye he's putting it back in the socket he
did the same thing with this throat and
leg he has the power to make living things
he made new body parts his powers are
the opposite of mine what who the hell are
you rambling on about no you don't stop
It's the newbie!
He came back to life!
Now it's coming after me!
Are you listening to me, Melone?
He transformed part of the bike into
some kind of weird roots! I'm stuck!
I have to get rid of the
parts that are stuck!
I need to get off this bike!
Damn it!
Did it turn into rocks again?
Problem!
He's after the turtle!
But I'll stop him dead in his tracks!
No, just simmer down, baby head!
Let him pick it up if he wants. But why?
Because after the fool goes for the turtle,
you'll eviscerate the little upstart.
The bike's spewing oil!
Not good!
Make sure he can never revive again!
All right, I got him!
I'll give you credit, you actually
managed to spook me a bit, bastardo!
Now get ready for the hurt, cause
I'm gonna rip your head off!
You have a talent for transforming
body parts into objects.
And it's inspired something in me.
Maybe it was simply fate?
Or perhaps it was our similar abilities?
that ultimately drew the
two of us to one another.
Whatever it was, thanks to your influence,
Golden Wind is a lot more capable.
Wait, where the hell did it go?
I know I tore off your freaking
wrist, so how'd it just disappear?
Tore it off, you say?
Sorry, but that's wrong.
I chose to let it go on purpose.
I'll do you a solid and
give you some free advice.
Your hand would be much better
served keeping yourself from harm,
rather than foolishly going after me. Huh?
Shove that advice up
your smug ass! Die! Die!
The hand you just severed has
already become a different
organism and is eagerly devouring
you from the inside out.
Yep.
You guessed it, it's now a piranha!
Can't get you out of my mind.
Since you'll be all I see.
I would give anything.
Just to make you understand me.
I don't give a damn about nothing else.
Freaking you is all I need.
I need your brain.
Tonight you got my time.
Tonight you
won't be sorry.
got my mind.
You got my mind.
I don't want to do something for you.
What must I say?
What must I do?
What must I do to show how
much I'm gonna freak you?
I must not sell you what must I do
to show how much
I'm gonna freak you.
Thank you.